trafficland.com 2006-11-11

# TrafficLand.com - Traffic Cameras, Traffic Video, Live Traffic Cams, U.S.

### 

Privacy Policy

TrafficLand.com takes the privacy of our users very seriously. The TrafficLand Company, which owns and operates the TrafficLand.com Web site, is dedicated to establishing a trusting relationship with its users, based on respect for personal identity and adherence to the highest industry standards for information privacy and security. This Privacy Statement addresses what kinds of information we collect from our users and how that information is used. By using the TrafficLand.com Web site, you agree to be bound by the terms of our Privacy Policy as follows:

### 

Types of Information TrafficLand.com Collects

In the ongoing operation and upgrading of the TrafficLand.com Web site, the TrafficLand Company, which owns and operates TrafficLand.com, collects and tracks certain types of information from all Web site visitors. This information is typically viewed in, and analyzed as a group of Web site use data for purposes of improving the service offerings and to communicate with our user community.

TrafficLand.com uses “cookies”, like most other Web sites, on some site pages. The information contained in these cookies, such as your User ID and Password or camera preference profiles allows users to enter the Web site and access the areas they are interested in more quickly. You are free to decline acceptance of TrafficLand.com cookies, but this may result in more time consuming log-in procedures and delays (or even denial of service) to certain Web site features. Use of some Web site services or requests for more information about upcoming TrafficLand services may require you to provide certain types of personal information such as, name, address, e-mail address, etc.

### 

How TrafficLand Uses Collected Information

TrafficLand uses information provided by TrafficLand.com users to improve service value and responsiveness to our customers as well as in fulfillment of requests for information or service changes.

### 

TrafficLand Policy on Sharing Collected Information

The TrafficLand Company will not share any information about individual Web site users’ specific camera viewing use with third parties. The TrafficLand Company will not sell or rent any personal information collected by TrafficLand.com to third parties. The TrafficLand Company will however share collected information about TrafficLand.com Web site users to comply with a court order or other legal process. The TrafficLand company will take all reasonable steps to safeguard the privacy of our Web site users’ information, when during the course of normal operations, there may be times when TrafficLand.com user information is under control of TrafficLand vendors or agents.

### 

Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on our Web sites are delivered to users through various third party advertising partners. Information about users visits to our Web sites, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on the sites. Third party advertising partners do not have access to personally identifiable information.

### 

Security

The TrafficLand Company takes every precaution to protect its user’s information. When users submit sensitive information via the company’s Web sites, that information is protected both online and offline.

When our registration / order forms ask users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry. While on a secure page, such as our paid subscription sign-up form, the lock icon (that appears on most Web browsers) becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ”surfing”.

TrafficLand also employs security measures to protect user information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing personnel or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers that store personally identifiable information are located in a secure environment.

### 

Links to Other Web Sites

TrafficLand.com will have links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any site that may have links to TrafficLand.com.

### 

Privacy Statement Updates

TrafficLand, Inc. and TrafficLand.com reserve the right to update, revise or make changes to our Privacy Policy at any time, without notice, and will update this Privacy Statement as needed to reflect changes in our services or business practices.
